xcoin.co.kr 2017-09-04

# 빗썸 - 대한민국 1등 가상화폐 거래소

#### Privacy Statement  
  
  In order to protect the personal information of the customer and to prevent the damage caused by leakage of personal information, BICTI Korea Corporation takes the customer's personal information very seriously, and we comply with the related laws and regulations that information and communication service, such as the Act on Promotion of Information Network Usage and Information Protection, and the Personal Information Protection Act  
  Our privacy policy is subject to change due to changes in laws or guidelines related to the protection of personal information or changes in our policies, so please check with us whenever you visit our site  
  
#### General Rules  
  
  BICTI Korea Corporation (hereinafter referred to as "the Company") is committed to protecting the privacy of users\' personal information and is committed to protecting the personal information that the user provides to the company while using the company\'s services Accordingly, the Company complies with the personal information protection regulations of the related laws and regulations and the personal information protection guidelines established by the Ministry of Information and Communication, which should be complied with by the providers of information and communication services, such as the Promotion of Information Network Usage and Information Protection Act  
  The Company will disclose through its Privacy Policy how and in what manner personal information provided by users is being used and what measures are being taken to protect personal information  
  The company discloses its privacy policy at the front page of the homepage so that users can easily view it at any time  
  The privacy policy of the company may change from time to time due to changes in the laws and guidelines of the government or changes in the company\'s internal policy Users are requested to check the privacy policy on the first page of the website from time to time   
  
#### 1 Agreement to collect personal information  
  
  The Company shall establish a procedure by which users can click the [Accept] button or the [Cancel] button on the contents of the company's personal information handling method or terms and conditions, if you click the [Accept] button, you agree to the collection of personal information   
  
#### 2\. Purpose of usage and collection of personal information  
  
  * Personal information means information about an individual who is alive and includes information that can identify the individual by the name, date of birth, etc included in the information (even if the information alone can not identify a particular individual, including those that can be easily identified and combined with) 
  * Personal information collected about individual customers and the purpose of collection and use are as follows

\- Name, ID, Password, Passport number (for foreigners only), Email address: Confirm your identity and confirm your customership  
\- Your bank account, a copy of your photo ID (cover up the details other than your birth date), mobile number: ID verification for payment and withdrawal  
\- Optional: Materials to provide personalized services  
\- Preventing fraudulent use of fraudulent customers and preventing unauthorized use  
  
#### 3\. Preventing fraudulent use of fraudulent customers and preventing unauthorized use  
  
  * When a user joins a customer to use a customership service, the company receives online information that is essential for providing the service   The essential information you receive when you sign up is your name, email address, and so on Also, in order to provide high quality service, user can input optional phone number and bank account number And we can also request personal information for statistical analysis or offer of prizes during surveys or events at the exchange 
  * We do not collect sensitive personal information (such as race and ethnicity, ideology, creed, hometown and homeland, political orientation and criminal record, health status, and sex life) that may be of concern to your basic human rights violations If we collect inevitably, we will ask for your prior consent And, in any case, the information you enter will not be used for any other purpose other than for the purpose previously provided to you, and will not be leaked out 

#### 4\. Retention and use period of personal information collected  
  
  * When a company collects personal information of a user, the period of retention is until customership termination (including withdrawal application, withdrawal of directorship) In addition, at the time of termination, the Company destroys the personal information of the user and instructs the third party to destroy the personal information provided to the third party However, if there is a necessity to preserve it in accordance with laws and regulations such as commercial law, we have transaction history and minimum basic information for the period of preservation prescribed by laws and ordinances In addition, we will keep your personal information for the duration of your promised period if you notify the user in advance of the period of retention, if the period of retention has not elapsed and if the individual consents of the user   
\- Records on contract or withdrawal of subscription: 5 years  
\- Record of payment and goods supply: 5 years  
\- Records of consumer complaints or disputes: 3 years
  * In the event that a user requests access to transaction information, etc, which is held with the consent of the user, the Company shall take measures so that it can be read and confirmed without delay

#### 5 Procedures and methods of personal information destruction  
  
In principle, the personal information of the user is destroyed without delay when the purpose of collecting and using the personal information is achieved And the procedure and method of destroying company's personal information is as follows   

  * Destruction procedure
  * \- The information entered by the user for customership purposes is transferred to a separate DB after the purpose has been achieved (in the case of paper, separate documents) According to internal policies and other relevant laws and regulations, it will be destroyed after a certain period of storage 
  * Destruction Methods

\- Personal information printed on paper is crushed or destroyed by crushing  
\- Personal information stored in the form of electronic files is deleted using a technical method that can not reproduce the record  
  
#### 6 Commitment of Personal Information  
  
  * BTC KOREA Co, Ltd Has been entrusting the following personal information to improve service And in accordance with the relevant laws and regulations, we provide the necessary information so that personal information can be safely managed when contracted 
  * The company's personal information processing agency and commissioned business are as follows
  * | Partners | Contents of trust business | Retention and use period of personal information  
---|---|---  
Danal Co, Ltd | Payment of cultural gift certificates, settlement of book cultural gift certificates, payment of game culture gift certificates, settlement of Happy Money cultural gift certificates | At the time of the withdrawal of the customership or until the termination of the trust agreement, when the statute establishes  
Think Full Co, Ltd | Service to prevent sign in stealing  
Settle Bank Co Ltd | Payment without account (virtual account)  
Shinhan Bank Co Ltd,  
(주)케이지이니시스 | 신용카드 결제 서비스  
IMI Corporation | B Point mall service  
Kookmin Bank Co, Ltd | KB Escrow Service  
Korea Credit Bureau Co, Ltd | Ipin self-certification service | Do not Save Separately (Information of the certified service provider)   
Korea Mobile Certification Co, Ltd | Mobile phone verification service  
Info Bank Co Ltd, | Send SMS  
Daou Technology Co, Ltd  

#### 7 Sharing and providing personal information collected  
  
  * The Company shall use the personal information of the users within the range of the purpose of collecting and using personal information, and shall not use it beyond the scope of this information or give it to any third party without prior consent of the user However, except in the following cases:  \- If there are special regulations in statutes such as the Act on Financial Real Name Transactions and Confidentiality, the Use and Protection of Credit Information, the Telecommunications Basic Act, the Telecommunications Business Act, the Local Tax Act, the Consumer Protection Act, the Bank of Korea Act and the Criminal Procedure Act  
\- In cases where it is judged in good faith that it is required by other laws (ex when there is a request from a government / investigative agency by lawful procedure under applicable law);  
\- Users agree to release in advance  
\- In violation of Terms of Service or Operating Principles, such as the Terms of Service and any other customer Services posted on the Website  
\- If you have reason to believe that your personal information must be disclosed in order to take legal action against it by causing mental or physical harm to others through our services  
\- When necessary for settlement of fees according to service provision  
\- When it is necessary for statistical writing, academic research or market research to provide a specific individual in an unidentifiable form
  * The Company may provide or share personal information with its affiliates or partners in order to provide better services to its users If we provide or share your personal information, you will need to know in advance what your affiliates are, what personal information items are shared or shared, why such personal information should be provided or shared, The individual will be informed and will be asked to obtain consent If the user does not consent, it will not be provided or shared with affiliates You may also withdraw your consent at any time, even if you consent to the provision of personal information 

#### 8 Regarding the user's personal information management (reading, correcting, deleting, etc)  
  
  * Users can log in to the BTC KOREA Corporation website (wwwxcoincokr) at any time and read or correct the user's personal information by changing the customer's information In addition, we will correct if you request by e-mail or in writing to the person in charge of personal information management on the company's homepage However, the customer ID and the name can not be corrected 
  * Users may withdraw your consent to withdraw or terminate your consent to the collection and use of your personal information and to withdraw your consent to third parties through e-mail, telephone, fax or other means In this case, the user must provide his / her ID and e-mail address for proof of identity 

#### 9 Matters concerning the operation of cookies(cookies)  
  
  * In order to provide customized services tailored to the customers, the company operates 'cookies' (cookies) to store and retrieve information from time to time The Company identifies your computer with respect to cookie management, but does not personally identify you 
  * The user has a choice of 'cookies' And the user can accept all cookies by selecting [Tools]> [Internet Options]> [Security]> [User Defined Level] in the web browser, check each time a cookie is saved, or refuse to store all cookies However, if you refuse to store all cookies, you will not be able to use the services provided by the company through cookies 

#### 10 Measures to Ensure the Safety of Personal Information  
  
The Company, pursuant to Article 29 of the Personal Data Protection Act, has the following technical, administrative and physical measures to ensure safety:

  * Minimization and training of personal information handling staff  
We designate employees who handle personal information and limit them to the person in charge, and implement measures to manage personal information
  * Regular self-audit conducted  
We conduct our own audits on a regular basis (quarterly basis) to ensure the safety of handling personal information
  * Establishment and implementation of internal management plan  
We have established and implemented an internal management plan for the safe handling of personal information
  * Encryption of personal information  
The personal information of the user is encrypted and stored and managed so that only the user can know it, and the important data is using separate security functions such as encrypting the file and transmission data or using the file lock function
  * Technical measures against hacking  
The company installs security programs, periodically updates and checks, installs systems from outside controlled areas, and technically and physically monitors and blocks them to prevent leakage and damage of personal information caused by hacking or computer viruses 
  * Restrict access to personal information  
We take necessary measures to control access to personal information through granting, modifying, and deleting access to the database system that handles personal information, and we control unauthorized access from outside by using an intrusion prevention system
  * Keeping connection logs and preventing forgery  
We keep and manage the records of access to the personal information processing system for at least six months, and we use security features to prevent forgery, theft and loss of access records
  * Using a lock for document security  
We keep the documents containing the personal information and the auxiliary storage medium in a safe place with a lock
  * Access control to unauthorized persons  
We keep separate physical storage places for personal information and set up access control procedures for them

#### 11 Personal Information Management Officer and Person in Charge  
  
  * The company is doing its best to make sure that you use the good information securely In case of any incidents that are against the notice to you in protecting personal information, the person in charge of personal information management is responsible
  * The responsibility for maintaining the security of the password of the user ID is related to the user himself / herself The company does not ask the user directly about the password in any way, so please be careful not to let the password leak to the other person Especially if you are online in a public place 
  * Despite the company's technical remedies, we are not liable for damage to information due to unforeseen accidents caused by basic network dangers such as hacking
  * The company has designated the personal information administrator and person in charge of collecting opinions and complaints about personal information, and the contact information is as follows [Personal information administrator]  
Responsibility: Representative Kim Dae Sik  
Charge: Representative Kim Dae Sik  
Position: CEO  
Customer Support Office: 1661-5566  
E-mail : [contact2@bithumb.com](mailto:contact2@bithumb.com)

#### 12 Duty of Notification  
  
The contents of the current Privacy Policy will be notified through the" Notice "on the website 7 days before the implementation of the changes, if there is any addition or deletion or modification of the contents due to the change of government policy or security technology
